HARRISON SMITH

Kansas City, MO (913) 424-8829 harrisonws320@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Innovative and creative professional with a drive to achieve mastery and help others realize their potential. Able to adapt communication and teaching methods to best suit an individual's needs. Fearless learner and compassionate leader with over a decade of experience producing quality work in demanding environments with strict parameters and deadlines.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

CENTRIQ'S IT CAREER PROGRAM KANSAS CITY, MO **Full Stack Web Development**

2023 to 2024

- Front End: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap, React
- Middle Tier: C#, .NET Core MVC, LINQ
- Back End: SQL, SQL Server

COLUMBIA UNIVERSITY NEW YORK, NY

2016 to 2021

M.A in Russian

- Graduated magna cum laude (3.84 GPA)
- Recipient of Dean's Fellowship
- Presented research at conferences for Columbia, Yale, Harvard, and Princeton

THE UNIVERSITY OF KANSAS LAWRENCE, KS

2009 to 2013

B.A. in Russian

- Graduated summa cum laude (3.93 GPA)
- Winner of Undergraduate Research Award through the Honors Department
- Awarded Post-Secondary Russian Scholar Laureate by the American Council of Teachers of Russian in 2011 and, again, in 2013

EXPERIENCE

HELPERS, INC.

Olathe, KS

Direct Support Worker

2021 to Current

- Develop my special needs client's verbal skills and serve as his tutor
- Supervise medication administration, personal hygiene, appointments, and recreational activities

COLUMBIA UNIVERSITY

New York, NY

Language Instructor & Graduate Teaching Assistant

2016 to 2021

- Graded and provided detailed feedback for students' papers and exams
- Maintained records of student attendance and grades throughout the course
- Delivered lectures and led group discussions for students
- Held office hours to assist students with their academic writing and Russian language

BROOKS FAMILY CARE

Olathe, KS

Pharmaceutical Dispensary Attendant

2013 to 2015

- Created a database to access every pharmaceutical representative's information, company, and record of branded drug samples
- Managed the sales, inventory, and orders of all prescriptions and supplements in practice's pharmacy
- Learned the use, efficacy, and contraindications of the medications and supplements
- Served as doctor's intermediary with pharmaceutical representatives and pharmacies

THE UNIVERSITY OF KANSAS

Lawrence, KS

Research Assistant for Dr. Ani Kokobobo

2012 to 2013

- Edited professor's article approved for publication
- Prepared comprehensive reports summarizing research on theoretical texts for her book Russian Writers and the Fin de Siècle: The Twilight of Realism (Cambridge University Press)
- Gathered data from libraries, literary journals, and online databases. for her book *Russian Grotesque Realism: The Great Reforms and the Gentry Decline* (Ohio State University Press)

SKILLS

- Programming Languages
- Web Technologies
- Copy Editing
- Problem-Solving

- Oral and Written Communication
- Public Speaking
- Leadership and Team Building
- Foreign Languages